import 'package:quiz_app/models/que.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. What is the name of the Curse occupying Yuji Itadoris body in "Jujutsu Kaisen?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Jogo',
      'b) Ryomen Sukuna',
      'c) Saturu',
      'd) Mahito',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. What is All Mights Quirk called in "My Hero Academia"?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Sugar Rush',
      'b) Tail',
      'c) Pop Off',
      'd) One For All',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. Which of these is another word for ninja?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Genjutsu',
      //Shinobi',
      'b) Shinobi',
      'c) Arigatho',
      'd) Gelato',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. What is Naruto mums name?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Kurama',
      'b) Kushina',
      'c) Haruno',
      'd) Carol',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. What team is Kakashi the leader of?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Twelve Guardian',
      'b) Team Rocket',
      'c) Team 7',
      'd) Taka',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. Who was the first Hashira that Tanjiro met in the mountains?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Shinobu Kocho',
      'b) Tengen Uzui',
      'c) Mitsuri',
      'd) Giyu Tomioka',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. Name this trainer who taught Tanjiro his water breathing technique?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Sankoji Urokodaki',
      'b) Kyojuro Rengoku',
      'c) Tengen Uzui',
      'd) Zenitsu',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8.  What type of sword does a Demon Slayer wield?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Steel Katana',
      'b) Nichirin Sword',
      'c) Adamantium Blade',
      'd) Kathana',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    '9. What was the name of the drum demon who was removed from the Kizuki?',
    crctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Enmu',
      'b) Akaza',
      'c) Muzan',
      'd) Kyugai',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
  question:
  '10. Who uses the Thunder Breathing form as their technique?',
  crctAnswerIndex: 0,
  options: [
    'a) Zenitsu',
    'b) Giyu',
    'c) Genya',
    'd) Muzan',
  ],
),
];